Hey, gentlemen.
Hey.
(Leonard:)- Hello.
- If any of you are looking for
(Sheldon:)something to do on Valentine's
Day, Amy and I'll be streaming
(Sheldon:)our first-ever live episode
of Fun With Flags.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome to join us
as we celebrate the timeless
(Sheldon:)love affair between
wind and flapping fabric.
(Leonard:)Penny and I have dinner
reservations that night,
(Leonard:)but any other time, no.
(Howard:)Sorry, Bernie and I
are breaking in
(Howard:)the new hot tub,
if you know what I mean.
(Sheldon:)Not a clue. Raj?
(Raj:)Spending Valentine's Day
with Emily.
(Leonard:)You don't sound
(Leonard:)very excited about it.
(Raj:)Oh, I am, I am.
I g... I guess
(Raj:)I'm still wondering if Emily
and I are right for each other.
(Howard:)Does this have to do with
that girl you had coffee with?
(Raj:)You mean the strong, sexy angel
I can't stop thinking about?
(Raj:)Who can say?
(Howard:)You've been talking about
breaking up with Emily forever.
(Howard:)Why don't you just do it already?
Yeah, just
(Leonard:)get it over with.
Well, you
(Raj:)say it like it's easy.
(Raj:)Have any one of you
(Raj:)ever broken up with anyone?
(Leonard:)No.
Not really.
(Sheldon:)You know, uh, once I ordered
an Uber by accident.
(Sheldon:)I just got in
and went somewhere.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪